(Sheldon:)Sheldon and the Hell Hound.
(Sheldon:)Or How I Lost My Hot Dogs.
Oh, um, ahem.
(Penny:)-I can come back.
-Don't be silly.
We're neighbors. We're gonna run into
each other. May as well get used to it.
(Penny:)Yeah. I guess you're right.
(Leonard:)-Used to it yet?
-Nope.
(Leonard:)Me neither.
Oh. Sheldon seemed to think
I'd be upset about you hanging out.
But I want you to know it's fine.
(Penny:)Oh, good.
Because his mother called me.
(Leonard:)-His mother?
-Yeah, she wants me...
(Penny:)...to take him shopping
for sheets and towels.
I was gonna do that.
Oh, well, then you do it.
I don't wanna do it. You can do it.
Okay, then you can take him
for shoes.
(Leonard:)I just took him for shoes.
(Penny:)Well, all I know is he says
they hurt his feet.